top of page

Log In

* Resources
    
* More

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Modified: 3/24/2024

​

This Privacy Policy forms part of the User Agreement and is incorporated by reference therein. Capitalized terms not defined herein will have the meanings set forth in the User Agreement and related policies. This Privacy Policy covers information you may provide to Libben LLC through the LittleBabyBooNursery.com, Littles.Store, connected YouTube, and connected Discord websites:

​

* what personally identifiable information of yours is collected;
    
* what organization is collecting the information;
    
* how the information is used;
    
* with whom the information may be shared;
    
* what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
    
* what kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company’s control; and
    
* how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Your Privacy is very important to us at Libben LLC. At Libben LLC, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of the visitors to our websites. In particular, we want you to know that Libben LLC is not in the business of selling, renting, or trading email lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Libben LLC by sending an email to [support@littlebabyboonursery.com](mailto:support@littlebabyboonursery.com).

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we’ve prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about Libben LLC’s practices so that you can make an informed decision.

1\. A Special Note About Children  
2\. Security  
3\. Information Libben LLC Collects  
4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information  
5\. User Account Cancellation Procedures  
6\. Notification of Changes to our Privacy Policy

#### 1\. A Special Note About Children.

Libben LLC requires all Users and users to be at least eighteen (18) years old to use any area of the Libben LLC Sites and requires that all Users and Users agree to the terms of the Age Verification Agreement in any interaction with us. Children are not eligible to use the Libben LLC websites and we ask that minors (under the age of eighteen (18)) not to submit any personal information to us.

​

#### 2\. Security.

​

2.1. Libben LLC has certain security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), which digitally encrypts your information as it is transferred from your computer to Libben LLC. We take the following measures to protect user information once it is received by the Site:

​

* employees have limited and controlled access to User information;
    
* measures have been taken so that servers and the data stored thereon are in a secure physical location;
    
* security software is used where Libben LLC determines it to be both appropriate and cost effective;
    
* employees are informed of all security protocol on a regular basis; and
    
* web security procedures are quality-assured weekly.

2.2. Although we strive to keep your personal information secure, no security measures are absolute and fool-proof and there is always a possibility that a security breach could occur, resulting in the release of a User’s data or information.

#### 3\. Information Libben LLC Collects.

3.1. Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth and efficient experience while you’re using Libben LLC’s website services, and to keep you informed of opportunities available on those services. This allows us to provide services and features that are designed to meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker. To this end, we may share general information you provide with Libben LLC-related entities worldwide, eg. its partners, affiliates, joint venturers, correspondents, associates and subsidiaries and their successors and assigns (collectively herein “Libben LLC Entities”).

​

3.2. When you join Libben LLC using our online registration form we may collect your email address, Username, real name, password, phone number, and other personal information listed in the registration form. Your Username is used throughout Libben LLC to identify you to other Users. Therefore, you should be aware that if you use your real name as your Username, this information will be visible to others who visit the Site. You can also join Libben LLC via co-branded pages or co-branded phone numbers using the co-branded registration forms available on such pages or phone numbers. Libben LLC will only use the information you provide to Libben LLC by joining Libben LLC through co-branded online registration forms and through Libben LLC’s online registration form in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you register as a User through any co-branded pages or phone numbers, Libben LLC may share your information with the partnering entity listed on the co-branded page. Prior to completing the registration on any co-branded page or phone number, Libben LLC will notify you if your information will be shared with the partnering entity listed on the co-branded page or phone number. By completing the registration on a co-branded page or phone number, you consent to Libben LLC’s disclosure of your information in accordance with the notices displayed during the co-branded registration process. In such event, the use of your information by the partnering entity will be subject to the terms and conditions of such partnering entity’s privacy policy, which may be less restrictive than this Privacy Policy.

3.3. We may use your email to contact you regarding account activities, new product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of Libben LLC and its affiliates. If you do not wish to receive such communications from Libben LLC you have the ability to stop receiving these mail communications by clicking "Unsubscribe" in the emails. You will, however, always receive administrative emails from Libben LLC that are related to the usage and functionality of Libben LLC. You may not opt-out of these administrative emails unless you cancel your Usership.

3.4. You can review, update and change some of your personally identifiable information including your email address, date of birth, and PIN number on the My Account page. 

3.5. Other than the profile information submitted by our Users, and except as noted herein, Libben LLC does not disclose any personally identifying information to other Users without your permission. If you choose to use Libben LLC forums, know that any personally identifiable information that you post can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you provide.

3.6. We use information we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, identify potential liabilities, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look at your User account information and transaction history to identify problems or resolve disputes. To have your account, personal information and transaction history erased from our records, please submit your request in writing:

Send us mail to the following mailing address:

Libben LLC

38713 Tierra Subida Ave #120

Palmdale, CA 93551

3.7. We may from time to time run promotions in which we ask Users or visitors for demographic information (like their Zip Code, State/Province or age). We may also run contests in which we ask Users or visitors for demographic information. We use this data to tailor your experience, showing content that we think you might be interested in and displaying the content according to your preferences. We also use demographic information to determine eligibility for certain promotions and contests.

3.8. From time to time Libben LLC may ask Users to participate in surveys. Such surveys may ask Users for contact information (like their email address). We may use contact information from our surveys to send you information about our company.

3.9. Libben LLC may contain links to other sites. Libben LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to review the policies of these sites.

3.10. Libben LLC also facilitates communication among Users through our YouTube and Discord Mail system. Messages sent via Mail are identified only by your Username.

3.11. Libben LLC may use certain information collected from our Users in aggregate form to tailor our Users’ experience at the Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. Libben LLC may also supplement the information you provide by purchasing information relating to you from third-party data providers. Libben LLC uses this information to improve its marketing and promotional efforts.

3.12. Libben LLC uses cookies.

Cookies are small amounts of data sent to a user’s browser from the Libben LLC Web servers and stored on a user’s computer’s hard drive. Libben LLC uses cookies to track the pages on Our Sites that our users visit. This allows us to collect aggregate information about usage on the Sites. Libben LLC may also use cookies to deliver content specific to Users’ interests, and to keep track of Users’ Usernames and passwords so that Users do not have to re-enter them during a session. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will be unable to use the Site.

3.13. Google Analytics.

When someone visits Libben LLC, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior. We do this to find out things such as a number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

3.14. Libben LLC uses your IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Generally, IP addresses tell us the location from which a person is connecting to us, what service provider the person is using and which parts of the Sites the Site user is visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that your session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous. We reserve the right to track IP addresses for the purposes of fraud prevention, and we reserve the right to release IP addresses to legal authorities.

​

3.15. If you send Libben LLC email correspondence, or if other Users or other third parties send us email or other correspondence regarding a particular User’s activities or postings on the Site, Libben LLC may collect such information.

3.16. Libben LLC strictly enforces and requires that all Users comply with its Anti-Spam Policy.

#### 4 Our Disclosure of Your Information.

​

4.1. Except as explicitly stated herein, we do not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifiable information to third parties. In addition to the other circumstances of disclosure described in this Privacy Policy, Libben LLC may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if you opt-in to having your personally identifiable information disclosed to such parties. When you consent to disclosure to such third parties, such third parties may use your information in accordance with their privacy policies, which may be less restrictive than this Privacy Policy. Libben LLC may also disclose your personal information to appropriate authorities and to banks associated with your User account in order to prevent or report suspected fraud and illegal activities, in order to prevent harm to any persons or if Libben LLC believes in good faith that the law requires it. In some cases, the government can compel the disclosure of information about you, and Libben LLC will comply, in which case you authorize it to do so. You also consent to Libben LLC disclosing information about you in connection with disputes involving other Users, and to actual or potential parties to a lawsuit or action that Libben LLC is or may become involved in, (a) if Libben LLC is required to do so, (b) if Libben LLC reasonably believes that such disclosures will potentially mitigate its liability, or (c) for Libben LLC to enforce its rights. Libben LLC may disclose some personally identifiable information to vendors and third-party service providers in connection with communications and payments to Users and other aspects of operating and promoting Libben LLC’s Site and Advisory Services. For example, Libben LLC uses other companies to deliver Libben LLC promotions, newsletter, and transaction emails, and we share your email address with this company unless you opt-out of receiving Libben LLC’s promotions. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter and mailing campaigns. 

4.2. Libben LLC may also exchange personally identifiable information among Libben LLC Entities worldwide. If you are registering on any sites controlled by Libben LLC Entities located in the European Union, your personally identifiable information must be disclosed to Libben LLC affiliates outside of the European Union in order to allow Users worldwide to contact and be contacted by you. Therefore, as a condition of your Usership you hereby agree and consent to the sharing of your personally identifiable information with Libben LLC and Libben LLC Entities worldwide.

#### User Account Cancellation Procedures.

​

If you decide you would like to cancel your User account on Libben LLC, you will need to do one of the following:

Send us an email including your User name and email address to [support@littlebabyboonursery.com](mailto:support@littlebabyboonursery.com) asking us to cancel.

or

Send us mail to the following mailing address:

Libben LLC

38713 Tierra Subida Ave #120

Palmdale, CA 93551

​

#### 6\. Notification of Changes.

​

6.1. From time to time, We may revise this Agreement. We reserve the right to do so, and You specifically agree that We have this unilateral right. You agree that all modifications or changes to this Agreement are in force immediately upon posting. The updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting, and the prior version is of no continuing legal effect unless the revised version specifically refers to the prior version and keeps the prior version or portions thereof in effect. To the extent any amendment of this Agreement is deemed ineffective or invalid by any court, the parties intend that the prior, effective version of this Agreement be considered valid and enforceable to the fullest extent.

6.2. If We change anything in this Agreement, We will change the “Last Modified Date” at the top of this Agreement. The Agreement is located at ([https://www.LittleBabyBooNursery/privacy).](https://www.littlebabyboonursery/privacy).) You agree to periodically re-visit this web page, and to use the “Refresh” button on Your browser when doing so. Upon each visit, You agree to note the date of the last revision to this Agreement. If the “Last Modified Date” remains unchanged from the last time You reviewed this Agreement, then You may presume that nothing in the Agreement has been changed since the last time You read it. If the “Last Modified Date” has changed, then You can be certain that something in the Agreement has been changed, and You agree that You will again review the Agreement in its entirety and that You will agree to its terms or immediately cease use of the Website. Your continued Use of the Website, after any such revision, shall be deemed to be Your acceptance of all revisions.

6.3. Waiver. If You fail to re-review this Agreement as required to determine if any of the terms have changed, You assume all responsibility for such omissions and You agree that such failure amounts to Your affirmative waiver of Your right to review the amended Agreement. We are not responsible for Your neglect of Your legal rights.

​

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with Libben LLC, please contact us.

​

Email: [support@littlebabyboonursery.com](mailto:support@littlebabyboonursery.com)

​

Mailing Address:

Libben LLC

38713 Tierra Subida Ave #120

Palmdale, CA 93551

Do Not Sell My Personal Information

© Libben LLC. All Rights Reserved.

bottom of page
